Guide to the Stanford University, Stanford Global Studies Division, records SC1213
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Stanford Global Studies Division, records
2006-2015
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University. Division of Global Studies.
SC1213
50200.32 megabyte(s)
4.5 Linear Feet
Stanford University. Division of Global Studies.
- Computer files
- Records
  - Islamic Studies, 2012-2014 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Program in International Relations, 2009-2011 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Center for South Asia, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Center for African Studies, 2011-2012 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Mediterranean Studies form, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - International Policy Studies, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Center for European Studies, 2011-2012 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - ICA, 2005-2013 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Center for Latin American Studies, 2012-2013 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Center for Buddhist Studies, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - General Management, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ICA Programs, 2006-2008 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - ICA Events 1/2, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - ICA Events 2/2, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - IPES Conference1/2, 9-10 Nov. 2007 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - IPES Conference 2/2, 9-10 Nov. 2007 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - ICA Events 1/2, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - ICA Events 2/2, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Global Health 1 of 2, 39535 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Global Health 2 of 2, 39535 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - ICA Events 1/2, 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - ICA Events 2/2, 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - ICA Events 1/2, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - ICA Events 2/2, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - CES, 40249 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Conference on Nationhood South Asia, 28-30 Apr. 2010 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - ICA Events 1/2, 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - ICA Events 2/2, 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - ICA Events 1/2, 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - ICA Events 2/2, 0 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2017-320
  - Posters, circa 2010-2015 (Box 1)